Everything works perfectly until the Russian terror begins again.
/EXPLOSION/
New films show a rare insight from Mariupol-
–As totally destroyed by Russian forces earlier during the war -
- And now annexed by Russia.
It is almost impossible to trust the material that comes from the Russian side.
It is selected propaganda material that is for us to get -
—The picture of a now flourishing city that is being rebuilt -
- And where all the inhabitants are happy with life - especially life in Russia.
Of course, we have started working according to Russian norms, and adopted Russian law.
Now everything is completely different.
The material was published on September 30 -
- On the anniversary of the illegal annexation of the Ukrainian regions -
- Luhansk, Donetsk, Zaporizjzja and Chenler.
This is what it looked like in Moscow the same day -
—When the anniversary, which in Russia is now referred to as the reunification day -
- Fired with pomp and standing.
It is symbolically important.
It is a way to show that you have had success in the war.
The whole war has been bought about -
—To one should liberate the Russian -speaking population of Ukraine -
- From "The Nazi rule", which is called Zelenskyj and his government.
This will be a clear picture that you want to show -
When the Proske Robert Fico proclaimed victorious in Slovakia's Val-
- Ringed the alarm bells in Brussels.
During the election, Fico has promised to strangle the support for Ukraine -
- And improve relationships with Russia.
Much indicates that Russia has affected the election and worked hard for it.
Several analysts have highlighted that the hard tone from Slovakia -
- Not so much for Ukraine.
I do not think so.
There is probably a deep unity political -
—That you have to resist Russia and support Ukraine -
- For the war not to expand and also affect their own countries.
However, I believe that dissatisfaction can lead to an increased split -